<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Ponmaalai IPL News</title><link>https://ponmaalai.example/kahoot/insights</link><description /><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:36:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><language>en-us</language><item><title>Gulbarga + Generation X lead pack</title><description>Total points: 4295. Avg points: 859.0. Delta vs demographic avg: +258.1. Signal: Generation X players born in Gulbarga are outperforming other location–generation mixes in this round. Fun fact – Gulbarga: Gulbarga, now Kalaburagi, was a key seat of the Bahmani Sultanate. Fun fact – Generation X: Gen X bridged the pre-digital and early-internet eras.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>ponmaalai:insight:1</guid></item><item><title>Tirunelveli + Generation X lead pack</title><description>Total points: 4246. Avg points: 849.2. Delta vs demographic avg: +248.3. Signal: Generation X players born in Tirunelveli are outperforming other location–generation mixes in this round. Fun fact – Tirunelveli: Tirunelveli is known for the iconic Nellaiappar Temple. Fun fact – Generation X: Gen X bridged the pre-digital and early-internet eras.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>ponmaalai:insight:2</guid></item><item><title>Thanjavur + Generation X lead pack</title><description>Total points: 7802. Avg points: 780.2. Delta vs demographic avg: +179.3. Signal: Generation X players born in Thanjavur are outperforming other location–generation mixes in this round. Fun fact – Thanjavur: Thanjavur was the Chola capital and is famed for Brihadisvara Temple. Fun fact – Generation X: Gen X bridged the pre-digital and early-internet eras.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>ponmaalai:insight:3</guid></item><item><title>Jaipur + Generation Z lead pack</title><description>Total points: 15405. Avg points: 770.2. Delta vs demographic avg: +169.3. Signal: Generation Z players born in Jaipur are outperforming other location–generation mixes in this round. Fun fact – Jaipur: Jaipur, the Pink City, was laid out with early modern urban planning. Fun fact – Generation Z: Gen Z is always-connected and highly visual in learning.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>ponmaalai:insight:4</guid></item><item><title>Rajahmundry + Millennial lead pack</title><description>Total points: 11540. Avg points: 769.3. Delta vs demographic avg: +168.4. Signal: Millennial players born in Rajahmundry are outperforming other location–generation mixes in this round. Fun fact – Rajahmundry: Rajahmundry on the Godavari is among Andhra’s oldest cultural hubs. Fun fact – Millennial: Millennials are the crossover generation for mobile + social.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>ponmaalai:insight:5</guid></item></channel></rss>